Luke Hackett

Computer Science Graduate from Trinity College Dublin with a First Class Honours Degree. Over the course of 4 years in university, Luke secured three internships spanning a range of companies during university, which has given him a diverse wealth of experience spanning many different technology stacks and company cultures.

EXPERIENCE

HubSpot, Dublin — *Software Engineering Intern*

lune 2020 - September 2020

- Despite short notice cancellation of my planned internship,
 Secured an Internship for my final Summer in University.
- Worked as a Full-Stack Intern, developing end-to-end features.
- Given responsibility for Product Rendering in email design previews, working on a complex Java rendering engine for html.
- Developed accompanying Front End, integrating product selection to preview with real products from web stores such as Shopify.

Microsoft, Dublin — *Software Engineering Intern*

June 2019 - August 2019

- Worked on designing and implementing search functionality in the Office store, as well as tangibly measuring its effectiveness.
- Became familiar with the Azure platform, as well as Azure Search specifically.
- Learned how to design and build large systems with a focus on quality.
- Accepted to work in Microsoft Seattle in 2021, however this opportunity was cancelled due to COVID-19

Travelport Digital, Dublin — Software Engineering Intern

June 2018 - August 2018

- Spent three months Interning in Travelport Digital working on Backend development for their TripAssist product team.
- Worked on multiple features and experienced deploying components through multiple development environments.
- Used technologies such as Ansible and Jenkins and programmed mainly in Groovy.

8 Hawthorne Grove, Clonskeagh, Dublin 14,

+353 85 185 7544

luke.hackett12@gmail.com https://lukehackett.me

SKILL

Programming:

Java, Groovy, C/C++, ARM Assembly, Python, RESTful, JSON, XML, SQL, JavaScript, C#, Go

Technologies:

Linux, Git, Jenkins, IntelliJ IDE, Vim, Gradle, Android, Electron, VueJS, ReactJS, NodeJS, Express, Firebase, Azure, Redux, Tensorflow, PyTorch, Keras

Management:

Jira(Kanban), GitHub Projects

Achievements

- First class honours degree in Computer Science from Trinity College Dublin
- Won Best Project in First Year Programming Project in College.
- Competed in Microsoft Ireland Hackathon making computer vision games for the "Lake".

EDUCATION

Trinity College, Dublin — Computer Science

September 2017 - Present

- Completed his degree in Computer Science with a First Class Honours (76%).
- Achieved 1.1 (80%) in his Final Year Project on Multi-Objective Deep Reinforcement Learning.
- Has completed four years of study and achieved an overall 1.1 for 1st year, a 2.1 in 2nd year, a 1.1 in 3rd year and a 1.1 in 4th year.

PROJECTS

MODRL Agent — Advanced Reinforcement Learning Agent

For my final year of Computer Science I researched and developed a Reinforcement Learning agent that learns multiple different objectives simultaneously. The agent leveraged Deep Learning to extract features from high state spaces and RL techniques to learn through experience. This is available on my Github here.

HQ Hacker — Trivia bot

I made a program that could take a screenshot of the popular trivia game 'HQ Trivia', and attempt to choose the correct answer out of the three provided. It did this by using an API to read the text then processes the language to try discern meaning before searching online. This is available on my Github here.

Secure Social — *Post Encrypted Messages*

I created a full social media site using ReactJs, with a firebase backend. This site was focused on being completely secure and transparent with its transactions. It used both asymmetric and symmetric key cryptography to ensure a secure key transmission. This project is available on my Github here.

BOI Balance Checker — Banking Application

As an introduction to Android development I made a Banking application for my bank as a substitute for their own application. The benefits of this is your account information is persistent therefore after setup the process of checking basic account information is simplified. This is in early stages of development and can be seen on my Github <a href="https://example.com/here/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/bases/